Viewers, whatever bondage, predicament, cage, infirmity, disease
Whatever it is! Whatever it is!
Generational curses - be released in the name of Jesus!
Be released in the name of Jesus!
I can hear you being released.
I can hear you being saved right now!
I can see you being delivered!
Say to your neighbor, "I have been delivered!"
I have been delivered!
I have been released!
In the name of Jesus!
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name.
Viewers all over the world, you have been waiting upon the Lord,
begin to release yourself in the name of Jesus!
That sickness, that disease - be removed in the name of Jesus!
That affliction, that setback be removed in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch the screen by faith in Jesus' Name.
Viewers all over the world,
whatever situation you are in
that Goliath in your life, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
That Goliath in your life, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
I say, power of resurrection, begin to flow."
In your blood, begin to flow!
In your kidney, begin to flow!
In your liver, begin to flow!
In your bones, begin to flow!
The power of resurrection, begin to flow!
In the name of Jesus!
Come out!
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name.
Thank you, Jesus, I'm free! Thank you, Jesus, I'm free!
In the name of Jesus, I am free! Thank you Jesus.
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name
Viewers all over the world, whatever bondage you are in,
be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Hardship, setback, limitation in progress - be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name
"I am free!"
Viewers all over the world, whatever critical situation that you are in...
are you on the sick bed? Familiar spirits, generational spirits,
limitation in progress, hardship, be released in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch the screen by faith in Jesus' Name
Be released in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch the screen by faith in Jesus' Name
Be released in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being released! You can go now.
Go and multiply!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch the screen by faith in Jesus' Name
In your business, go and multiply!
In your career, go and multiply!
In your health, go and multiply!
In your marriage, go and multiply!
In your finances, go and multiply!
In Jesus' name!
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name
Who are you?
Speak Out!
How do you operate in her?
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name
What have you done to her marriage?
Who are you? Who are you in this body?
Satan
The devil?
Yes!
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name
We are many!
Prophet T.B Joshua ministering prayer at the SCOAN prayer line in Jesus name.
Satan. Satan. Satan
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name
What have you done to her marriage?
I haven't done anything in her marriage. I just want to kill her!
How did you enter her?
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name
By medicine. I gave her medicine.
I am from Sudan!
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministering prayer at The SCOAN prayer line in Jesus' name
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.